RINGO CHUI

Objective

I am a **Computer Science** student with three years of education in the field and eight months of hands-on IT experience who is looking for opportunities to broaden horizons with software-related work. Aiming to use my technical knowledge and adaptable mindset to help as one of your developers.

Education

SEP 2021 - PRESENT

Computer Science, Bachelor of Science / York University Lassonde School of Engineering SEP 2018 – APR 2021

Computer Engineering Technology Diploma / Seneca College Newnham Campus

- President's Honour List (4 Semesters)
- Awarded a "High Honours" standing graduating with a GPA of 4.0

Experience

SEP 2019 - MAY 2020

Helpdesk Analyst (Co-op) / Esri Canada Limited

Acted as a primary contact for internet users with regards to IT support. Contributed to ongoing customer support services and worked on several IT infrastructure related projects and initiatives

JUN 2014 - PRESENT

Summer Camp Committee Member / St. Agnes Kouying Tsao Catholic Church

Planned and executed for months as a member of a team to produce a successful summer camp experience. Promoted from counsellor to committee member as of June 2018.

Soft Skills

- Fluent in Cantonese Chinese
- Problem solver
- Adaptable team player

Projects

- Scrolling web game
- Battleship made in Python with rudimentary AI
- Self-Driving RC Car

Certificates

- AZ-900: Microsoft Azure Fundamentals
- CCNA Routing and Switching: Introduction to Networks

Technical Skills

- General programming concepts
- Programming Languages: C, C++, C#, Python, Java, JavaScript/TypeScript, CSS/HTML, SQL
- Frameworks/Libraries: ASP.NET, React, Express
- Proficient with Microsoft Office Applications and Adobe Applications
- Knowledge with field related technologies: OrCAD, Git, SQLite, Oracle SQL Developer, PostMan, Node.JS